<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Розрахунок спектру</string>
	<!-- main layout -->
	<string name="main_activity_title">Введіть початкові значення</string>
    <string name="period_title">Період - T</string>
	<string name="period_details">Період сигналу - найменший проміжок часу, через який повторюються миттєві значення сигналу.</string>
	<string name="time_title">Ширина імпульсів - t</string>
	<string name="time_details">ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина ширина</string>
	<string name="amplitude_title">Амплітуда - h</string>
	<string name="amplitude_details">амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда амплітуда</string>
	<string name="expandable_text">We Sanchhaya Education Pvt. Ltd., are registered and headquartered
        at BC 227, 2nd Floor, Matrix Business Tower, B4, Sector 132, Noida, UP-201301, hereinafter
        referred to as GeeksforGeeks. We also offer paid Courses managed by Sanchhaya Classes Pvt. Ltd.
        with registered office address B-142, Vishwash Park, Uttam Nagar, New Delhi, North Delhi, Delhi, India, 110059.
        At GeeksforGeeks, we value your trust and  respect your privacy. This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”)
        applies to the treatment of personally identifiable information submitted by, or otherwise obtained from,
        you in connection with the associated application (“Application”). The Application is
        provided by GeeksforGeeks (and may be provided by Geeksforgeeks on behalf
        of a GeeksforGeeks licensor or partner (“Application Partner”).
        By using or otherwise accessing the Application, you acknowledge that you accept the practices
        and policies outlined in this Privacy Statement.</string>
	<string name="button_main">Розрахувати спектр</string>
	<!-- second layout -->
	<string name="second_activity_title">Значення амплітуд</string>
	<string name="button_second">Побудувати графік</string>
	<!-- third layout -->
	<string name="third_activity_title">Графік</string>
	<string name="button_third_text">Повернутись</string>
</resources>
